The first
thing to
note
about
Iranian
traditions
is the
emphasis
on
hospitality.
Iranians
take
great
pride in
their
hospitality,
and it is
considered
rude to
decline
an
invitation
to
someone's
home.
Upon
arrival,
guests
are
offered
tea,
fruit,
and
pastries,
and often
a full
meal is
prepared.
Another
important
aspect of
Iranian
traditions
is the
celebration
of
Nowruz,
or
Persian
New Year.
This
holiday
marks the
beginning
of spring
and is
celebrated
with a
variety
of
traditions,
including
cleaning
one's
home,
visiting
family
and
friends,
exchanging
gifts.
One of
the most
iconic
symbols
of Nowruz
is the
haft-sin
table,
which is
decorated
with
seven
items
that
start
with the
letter
"S" in
Persian,
symbolizing
new
beginnings,
rebirth,
and
prosperity.