Muscle
cars are
a true
symbol of
American
automotive
culture.
These
powerful
vehicles,
typically
produced
in the
1960s and
1970s,
are known
for their
large
engines
and
impressive
performance
capabilities.
One of
the most
iconic
muscle
cars is
the Ford
Mustang.
This
vehicle,
which was
first
introduced
in 1964,
quickly
became a
cultural
icon
thanks to
its sleek
design
and
impressive
speed.
Other
notable
muscle
cars
include
the
Chevrolet
Camaro,
the Dodge
Charger,
and the
Pontiac
GTO.
These
vehicles
were
designed
to be
fast and
powerful,
and they
continue
to be
popular
collector's
items
today.
Whether
you're a
fan of
classic
cars or
simply
appreciate
raw
power,
muscle
cars are
sure to
leave a
lasting
impression.