A
supernova
is the
explosive
death of
a star,
occurring
at the
end of a
star's
life
cycle.
These
cosmic
events
are among
the most
powerful
and
energetic
in the
universe,
releasing
as much
energy as
the sun
is
expected
to emit
over its
entire
life.
Supernovae
can be
classified
into two
main
types:
Type I
and Type
II.
Type I
supernovae
occur in
binary
star
systems
where a
white
dwarf
star
accretes
matter
from a
companion
star
until it
reaches a
critical
mass,
leading
to a
thermonuclear
explosion.
Type II
supernovae,
on the
other
hand,
result
from the
core
collapse
of a
massive
star,
causing a
catastrophic
explosion
that
blasts
the
star's
outer
layers
into
space.