The
traditional
religions
of Nepal
are an
integral
part of
the
country's
cultural
heritage.
Nepal is
known for
its rich
diversity
in terms
of
religion,
with
Hinduism
and
Buddhism
being the
two main
religions
practiced
in the
country.
Hinduism
is the
dominant
religion
in Nepal,
with
approximately
81% of
the
population
identifying
as
Hindus.
The
religion
has a
strong
presence
in the
country,
with many
temples,
shrines,
and holy
sites
dedicated
to
various
deities.
The
Pashupatinath
Temple in
Kathmandu
is one of
the most
sacred
Hindu
temples
in the
world,
attracting
thousands
of
devotees
and
tourists
every
year.
Buddhism,
on the
other
hand, is
the
second-largest
religion
in Nepal,
with
approximately
9% of the
population
identifying
as
Buddhists.
The
religion
has a
long
history
in Nepal,
with many
Buddhist
monasteries,
stupas,
and
shrines
scattered
throughout
the
country.
The
birthplace
of
Gautama
Buddha,
Lumbini,
is
located
in Nepal
and is an
important
pilgrimage
site for
Buddhists
from all
over the
world.
In
addition
to
Hinduism
and
Buddhism,
there are
also
other
traditional
religions
practiced
in Nepal,
such as
Kiratism,
Bon, and
Jainism.
These
religions
have
their
unique
beliefs,
practices,
and
traditions,
adding to
the rich
tapestry
of
Nepal's
cultural
heritage.
Despite
the
diversity
in
religious
beliefs,
there is
a high
degree of
religious
tolerance
and
harmony
in Nepal.
People of
different
religions
live
together
in peace,
respecting
each
other's
beliefs
and
practices.
This
religious
harmony
is an
essential
aspect of
Nepal's
cultural
identity
and is
something
that the
country
takes
great
pride in.