Paying
off your
mortgage
early
might
seem like
a smart
financial
decision.
However,
there are
several
reasons
why it
may not
be the
best
idea.
Firstly,
you could
miss out
on the
opportunity
to invest
your
money
elsewhere
and
potentially
earn
higher
returns
than the
interest
rate on
your
mortgage.
By paying
off your
mortgage
quickly,
you're
essentially
locking
away
funds
that
could
have been
used for
other
investments.
Secondly,
keeping
your
mortgage
can
provide
tax
benefits.
In many
countries,
including
Nigeria,
homeowners
can
deduct
their
mortgage
interest
from
their
taxable
income,
reducing
their
overall
tax
burden.
If you
pay off
your
mortgage
early,
you lose
these
potential
tax
savings.