Fresh
cabbages
are a
versatile
and
nutritious
vegetable
that can
be
enjoyed
in many
ways.
They come
in
various
shapes
and
sizes,
such as
round or
pointed
heads,
and range
from
tight,
compact
varieties
to
loose-leafed
ones.
When
selecting
a
cabbage,
look for
one that
feels
heavy for
its size,
has crisp
leaves,
and is
free from
blemishes
or
discolouration.
To
prepare
cabbage,
first
remove
any
damaged
outer
leaves.
Then
rinse it
thoroughly
under
cold
running
water.
You may
choose to
cut the
cabbage
into
wedges,
slices,
or shred
it using
a knife
or food
processor.
Cooking
methods
include
boiling,
steaming,
sautéing,
stir-frying,
or even
roasting
– making
it a
perfect
addition
to soups,
stews,
salads,
slaws,
and side
dishes.
Don’t
forget
that
fermented
cabbage,
known as
sauerkraut,
provides
beneficial
probiotics
and adds
depth to
sandwiches,
hot dogs,
and other
meals.